Turned it on after all these years Dust on the cartridge dust
오랜 세월 만에 다시 켰어, 카트리지엔 먼지가.
on the screen Three empty slots where stories lived Like someone
화면 위에도. 이야기가 살았던 세 개의 빈 슬롯, 마치 누군가
erased a dream But the cursor blinks on slot one And it
꿈을 지운 듯. 하지만 커서는 첫 번째 슬롯에서 깜빡거리고, 그것은
whispers something new Start again from nothing Every blank page
새로운 무언가를 속삭여. 아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해. 모든 빈 페이지는
holds a song All the maps are waiting Undrawn worlds where I
노래를 담고 있어. 모든 지도가 기다리고 있어. 내가 속할, 그려지지 않은
belong Hundred hours gone without a trace No saved princess
세상들. 백 시간이 흔적도 없이 사라졌어. 구한 공주도 없어,
no final score But my hands still know the buttons And the
최종 점수도 없어. 하지만 내 손은 여전히 버튼들을 알아. 그리고 그
music plays once more So the cursor blinks on slot one And I
음악은 다시 한번 연주돼. 그래서 커서는 첫 번째 슬롯에서 깜빡이고, 나는
press it knowing now Start again from nothing Every blank page
이제 알면서 그걸 눌러. 아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해. 모든 빈 페이지는
holds a song All the maps are waiting Undrawn worlds where I
노래를 담고 있어. 모든 지도가 기다리고 있어. 내가 속할, 그려지지 않은
belong Start again from nothing Every blank page holds a
세상들. 아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해. 모든 빈 페이지는
song All the maps are waiting Undrawn worlds where I belong
노래를 담고 있어. 모든 지도가 기다리고 있어. 내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상들.